In the last video, we discussed the purpose of rebalancing,
在上个视频中 我们讨论了再平衡的目的
costs incurred during rebalancing,
再平衡产生的成本
and we also chatted about a way to estimate those costs.
并且讨论了估算成本的方式
But how do you know when to rebalance a portfolio?
但是怎么知道何时再平衡投资组合？
There are two types of events that trigger the rebalancing decision,
有两种事件会促使做出再平衡决策
cash flows and changes in the underlying parameters of the stock return model.
现金流和股票收益率模型的参数发生变化
Cash flows are movements of money into and out of a portfolio.
现金流是指现金流入和流出投资组合
For a portfolio of stocks,
对于股票投资组合来说
the most common forms of cash flows are dividends,
最常见的现金流形式是股息
capital gains and new contributions.
资本利得和新的出资
For example, an investor receives dividend payments when he loans a stock.
例如 当投资者做多股票时 获得了股息付款
However, when he has shorted a stock,
但是 当他做空股票时
he is obligated to pay the balance of dividend payments
则需要将发放给股东的股息付款余额
issued to shareholders to the person who has loaned him the stock.
支付给股票贷款方
Capital gains and losses are the increases or
资本利得和损失是指
decreases in value of the assets in the portfolio,
投资组合资产价值的上涨或下跌
but these are unrealized until the assets are sold at
但这些是未实现的资本利得或损失
which time they become realized capital gains and contribute to cash flows.
直到资产被出售 这时候变成已实现的资本利得并进入现金流
New contributions consist of new investments in the fund or portfolio under management.
新的出资是指对基金或投资组合做出新的投资
The simplest way to adjust for cash flows is to
调整现金流的最简单方式是
buy and sell stocks using the current portfolio weights,
根据当前投资组合权重买卖股票
but when some assets appreciate and some depreciate,
但是当某些资产上涨 某些资产下跌时
the weights which represent the fraction of the portfolio invested in each asset change.
代表投入每个资产的资金所占比例的权重会变化
A portfolio manager can take advantage of cash flows to adjust the under
投资组合经理可以利用现金流调整权重不足
weighted or over weighted portfolios to return to the target asset allocation.
或权重过高的投资组合 并回到目标资产分配水平
Changes in model parameters do not automatically trigger rebalancing.
模型参数的变化不会自动触发再平衡
In this case, the portfolio manager must decide whether the parameter change is
在这种情形下 投资组合经理需要判断参数变化是否足够大
large enough to warrant incurring transaction costs to rebalance.
即使考虑到交易成本 也要再平衡
As a portfolio manager,
作为投资组合经理
you need to constantly monitor the parameters used
你需要不断监控投资组合采用的参数
in your portfolio and be ready to rebalance when needed.
并在需要时再平衡
Parameters can change at anytime.
参数可能随时会变化
For example, many types of corporate actions such as mergers and
例如 很多类型的企业行为（例如合并和收购）
acquisitions or changes in management may impact the model's parameters.
或管理层变化可能会影响模型参数
When a portfolio manager suspects that a parameter has changed,
当投资组合经理怀疑参数变化了时
she will re-estimate the model to come up with the optimal weights,
她将重新估算模型并获得最佳权重
then she will decide if the portfolio should be rebalanced by
然后权衡再平衡的优势以及不足之处 例如交易成本
weighing the benefits of rebalancing with the downsides such as transaction costs.
并判断是否需要再平衡
The most common rebalancing strategies are
最常见的再平衡策略
based on rebalancing at set temporal frequencies,
会根据设定的时间频率再平衡
or rebalancing when portfolio weights change by a certain threshold amount.
或者当投资组合权重变化达到某个阈值时再平衡
One strategy is to rebalance at a set temporal frequency, daily, monthly,
一种策略是以设定的时间频率再平衡
quarterly, annually or at another frequency,
例如每日 每月 每季 每年等等
regardless of the changes in the sizes of the portfolio weights.
无论投资组合权重的变化大小是多少
This temporal frequency typically comes from the original time horizon of optimization.
这种时间频率通常是根据原始的优化时间范围确定的
When a portfolio manager models his portfolio,
当投资组合经理对投资组合建模时
he will often optimize it using data from a chunk of time of some duration.
通常会使用某个时期的数据优化模型
For example, if a portfolio is model based on month long chunks of data,
例如 如果投资组合模型基于一个月的数据
the optimal weights are only valid for a month and so rebalancing is performed monthly.
最优权重只有一个月有效期 所以每月都会再平衡
The threshold base strategy calls for rebalancing
对于阈值再平衡策略
the portfolio only when the portfolio weights have
只有当投资组合权重与目标权重的差异
drifted from the target ones by a predetermined threshold such as 1%, 5% or 10%.
超过提前设定的阈值（例如 1% 5% 或 10%）时 才会再平衡
Since rebalancing does not occur at predetermined times,
因为再平衡并不按照预定的频率发生
it can happen as frequently as daily,
所以可能会每日发生一次
but also as infrequently as yearly.
也可能会每年发生一次
These strategies can also be combined,
还可以将这两种策略结合到一起
such that rebalancing is performed on a scheduled basis but only when
按照预定的时间表再平衡
the portfolio weights have drifted from the target ones by a predetermined threshold,
但是仅在权重与目标的差异超过某个阈值时才再平衡
thus, both criteria must be fulfilled.
所以两个条件都必须满足
On the scheduled rebalancing date,
在预定的再平衡日期
if the change in the portfolio weights is less than the threshold,
如果投资组合权重的变化小于阈值
rebalancing won't be performed.
则不再平衡
Also, if the portfolio weights drift by
此外 如果投资组合权重
more than the threshold before the scheduled rebalancing date,
在预定的再平衡日期之前超过了阈值
rebalancing won't be performed.
也不再平衡